[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which U.S. state has been nicknamed The Cornhusker State?", "correct_answer": "Nebraska", "incorrect_answers": ["Nevada", "Ohio", "Wyoming"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What day of the week is associated with the blue color in Thailand?", "correct_answer": "Friday", "incorrect_answers": ["Sunday", "Wednesday", "Monday"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement about Bambi is true?", "correct_answer": "Hitler banned Bambi.", "incorrect_answers": ["Tyrus Wong was the head animator for Bambi, Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs and Cinderella.", "Bambi is played continuously from 9 A.M. to 6 P.M. at the Dover Theater in New York City.", "At first Walt Disney did not want to make the film but his brother, Roy, urged him to."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the 1980 movie \u201cThe Shining\u201d, based on a Stephen King novel and starring Jack Nicholson?", "correct_answer": "Stanley Kubrick", "incorrect_answers": ["Francis Ford Coppola", "Alfred Hitchcock", "Steven Spielberg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "She is regarded as the most famous blonde of all times.", "correct_answer": "Marilyn Monroe", "incorrect_answers": ["Marlene Dietrich", "Eva Brown", "Madonna"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Finish the nursery rhyme:\nPeter Piper picked a peck of .........", "correct_answer": "pickled peppers", "incorrect_answers": ["pickled pickles", "pickles", "Peppers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For which university did fictional character Forrest Gump play college football, earning All-American honors?", "correct_answer": "University of Alabama", "incorrect_answers": ["University of Florida", "Auburn University", "University of Georgia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the 1985 movie A View to a Kill?", "correct_answer": "John Glen", "incorrect_answers": ["Michael Ritchie", "Paul Wendkos", "Ferdinand Fairfax"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actress stars as the  young  pregnant Juno MacGuff in the movie Juno.", "correct_answer": "Ellen Page", "incorrect_answers": ["Allison Janney", "Danielle Clarke", "Olivia Thirlby"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of what descent is Leonardo DiCaprios mother, Irmelin?", "correct_answer": "German", "incorrect_answers": ["Jewish", "Irish", "Polish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vegetarians can get all the proteins they need through non-meat food sources.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 2005 movie Rumor Has It was about a young woman who finds out her grandmother may have been the inspiration for The Graduate character Mrs. Robinson.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]